<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lists on sMark Notes [DRAFT]</title>
    <link>https://mmt.github.io/smark-notes/lists/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lists on sMark Notes [DRAFT]</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Copyright Mark M. Tobenkin 2020</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 10:20:03 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mmt.github.io/smark-notes/lists/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Interesting Software</title>
      <link>https://mmt.github.io/smark-notes/lists/interesting_software/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 10:20:03 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmt.github.io/smark-notes/lists/interesting_software/</guid>
      <description>This post is a running list of some software projects I want to look into more or have found useful in the paste.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interesting Algorithms / Concepts</title>
      <link>https://mmt.github.io/smark-notes/lists/interesting_algorithms/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 10:07:52 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmt.github.io/smark-notes/lists/interesting_algorithms/</guid>
      <description>This post will just be a running collection of useful algorithms / concepts I want to remember.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interesting Papers and Books</title>
      <link>https://mmt.github.io/smark-notes/lists/interesting_papers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 11:30:31 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmt.github.io/smark-notes/lists/interesting_papers/</guid>
      <description>Navigation and Kalman Filtering Kalman Filtering  Book: Principles of GNSS, Inertial, and Multisensor Integrated Navigation Systems Book: Advanced Kalman Filtering, Least-Squares and Modeling: A Practical Handbook Book: Stochastic Models, Estimation and Control: Volume 1  Inertial Sensors  IMU Error State Modeling for State Estimation and Sensor Calibration: A Tutorial  Rotation Formalisms  Quaternion kinematics for error-state Kalman filter Attitude Error Representations for Kalman Filtering On the rotation vector differential equation  Visual navigation  Keyframe-Base Visual-Inertial Odometry Using Nonlinear Optimization High-Precision, Consistent EKF-based Visual-Inertial Odometry  Lie Theory in Estimation  A micro Lie theory for state estimation in robotics  More general Math Lie Theory  Book: Naive Lie Theory  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
